The final exam of Xingyun, the prosperous Yun State.
The top scholar of Xingyun
should be approved by the people of the Yun State.
All the poetry has been compiled into a book.
You can buy it at Huayue Tower and Yun Bookshop.
The top ten
in the Xingyun Ranking
will enter the final exam of Xingyun.
Praise the prosperity of the Yun State.
What is the final exam of Xingyun?
Why is it so complicated?
I just want to see Mr. Cheng's play.
It should be asking us to buy his books.
It's really for buying books.
Quick, before she buys them all.
Right, she really could do this.
So many.
Quick, quick, quick, let's go.
My lady,
you're up this late,
sharpening your sword.
Planning to use it on me?
No.
Then,
are you going to fight with Bai Yanliang?
Why fight in the middle of the night?
Why are you up at this hour?
You went out with Bai Yanliang,
and you didn't say a word when you came back.
I'm your husband.
I'm just concerned about you.
What's going on?
I...
I miss my mother.
That's a unique way
of showing your affection.
So,
she got hurt because she saved someone.
I knew it.
My mother never missed a target.
Could it be Bai Yanliang?
What a coincidence.
So,
Bai Yanliang is here to repay the favor.
What does it have to do with me?
He couldn't marry me.
He said
he was afraid you would hurt me.
Hurt you?
Who dares? I don't.
My dear,
what kind of person
is your mother?
My mother
is the best escort in the world.
But the escorts of our Su family
protect people, not hurt them.
You should
have your own things to do.
Things to do?
So,
I have to protect the escort agency for my mother.
I can't let her down.
Your mother would be proud of you.
Thank you
for listening to me.
Cheng is so talented.
I want one too.
Give me two.
Yicheng,
what's going on at the Huayue Pavilion?
Meng Feifei said this is what happens
when the Star Chart is released.
Don't grab, there's enough for everyone.
What else did she say?
She asked me to take you through the back door.
Why?
Look at him.
What's so good about Cheng Qi?
Cheng Qi is the best.
Only ignorant women like you
would appreciate Cheng Qi.
Mr. Ling is the best.
When Mr. Cheng comes,
he will make you and your Mr. Ling
feel ashamed.
Mr. Ling won't hang around here
like Cheng Qi.
That's not what a gentleman would do.
Guys,
we can't let him bully Cheng.
Go!
Beat him!
Right.
What are you doing?
You deserve this for talking nonsense.
Don't hit his face.
This is too crazy.
Meng Feifei really is a prophet.
Go.
Go through the back door.
These are all from the girls who admire you.
They prepared for your final exam.
Why?
You are the top of the Starry Cloud Conference.
Thanks to you,
the business of our Huayue Tower
is getting better and better.
Can I get a discount on my drinks?
No.
But your drinks for this month
have been paid for.
Handsome,
dashing, well-dressed, and talented.
My Lord.
Just say it.
Bai Yanli is missing.
I let him go.
Everyone has their own aspirations.
He must have found what he wants to do.
He should have left long ago.
He's just showing off.
He's just showing off to us.
He works tirelessly for no pay.
He works himself to the bone for no life.
You two are shameless!
Go to work!
My Lord, there are no new orders
in and around the city.
We only have these few left.
I'll figure something out.
While you have the time,
you two should go prepare the armor and weapons.
Gong Xi, Fatt Choy.
Come and help!
Hurry up!
Hold it. I'll go first.
Cheng Yicheng, hold it. Use your strength.
Cheng Yicheng, use your strength.
Let's go back.
Go.
What happened?
I'm afraid we can't
stay in the Huanyue Tower anymore.
A thief broke into my room.
No way.
In broad daylight,
who's that bold?
How would I know?
And there are always
so many people outside my door.
I can't focus on writing lyrics.
My lady,
you saw today
so many girls chasing me.
I'll get rid of them.
No need.
So what do you want?
Tell me.
I want to go back to the Escort Agency to write lyrics.
No.
With all these people blocking the entrance,
how can we take on any more escort missions?
My lady, I don't care.
I can't stay at the Huayue Tower anymore.
And,
when Yicheng and I fled, we were too hasty.
We didn't bring a lot of things.
You can take it as escorting me.
Bring them back for me.
Su Shi Escort Agency never gives credit.
Is the business
not going well recently?
You even have to calculate with your husband.
Look at the yard.
It's full of escort vehicles.
How can it be good?
Even so, you still want to come back to write lyrics.
Your girls have nothing to do,
and they mess up the last business of the escort agency.
It's time for me to show my skills.
What skills do you have?
If you want to bring business to the escort agency,
why are you in my Moon God Pavilion?
People are blocking me at the entrance of the escort agency.
My wife doesn't like it.
You didn't ask me if I like it.
I'm just building up the reputation of the Moon God Pavilion.
Mr. Meng,
I've heard recently
that the Moon God Pavilion
has sold a lot of things related to me.
I want to make some peripheral products.
You take 70%, I take 30%.
I'll also publish a novel about you and Su Biao.
A novel?
What novel?
It's about your daily life.
I don't have time for that.
Don't worry. I've found someone.
Mr. Cheng,
30%.
Since you are in full charge,
I'll just give you 10%.
Okay.
It's a deal.
Deal.
Goodbye.
What are they doing here?
To escort.
I thought they were here to rob.
They are all escorts from the city.
Is it possible that
my uncle went out to find a job?
It has nothing to do with him.
These are all escort orders brought by my son-in-law.
You can go to escort first.
I'll be right back.
This way, please.
So handsome!
Take a look.
All are fine wine.
Please take a look.
Thank you.
How's that?
I'm good at matchmaking, right?
Mr. Cheng is indeed a reliable man.
He should be preparing for the Starry Night Gala,
instead of wasting time here.
I have to take him back.
He's doing this for you.
He said the business of the Escort Agency is not good,
so he came here to find business.
I was just joking with him.
It's not that serious.
Only you know that.
Don't be fooled by his usual laughter.
In his heart,
he knows what is important.
Is he as good as you say?
I like you.
Are you married?
Would you like to marry me?
Thank you for your love.
I'm already married.
She is the head of the Su's Escort Agency.
She is my wife.
Liar!
He's a liar!
I don't want to stay here.
Go, he's a liar!
Liar!
I'm not afraid of being cheated.
How's that?
Cheng Qi is really good, isn't he?
Thank you.
Someone broke into Cheng Qi's room and took things.
Did he lose anything important?
He doesn't have anything valuable.
It's just a woman who wants to be a thief.
In that case,
Ying,
arrange for someone
to prepare the study in the courtyard.
My lady, are you planning to have him stay there?
I'll go later.
For now,
I'll stay with you.
What's the matter? Why so hesitant?
The Young Master has arrived,
with whom?
Mr. Ling,
and some other noble young men.
And...
His Lordship wants to see you.
I see.
As long as I'm here,
you can rest assured
about the poetry meeting.
You're right.
My lord,
Mr. Ling has been
is Mr. Ling.
Thank you, Lord Zhang.
Thank you, Miss.
What?
Do I need to repeat it?
Brother.
The rules have been announced.
Lord Yue will also attend.
I dare not decide
who will be the champion.
Mr. Ling, don't worry.
If she can't decide,
I'll decide for you.
I toast to Lord Zhang.
Why get married so early?
Yeah, why marry a bodyguard?
I wanted to marry Cheng.
Do you really have to do this to him?
You know
how much effort we've put in
to help Cheng become the top scholar.
But it's normal for a man like him
to get married at an early age.
But he didn't marry a noble lady
or a refined lady.
He married a bodyguard
and even lived in her house.
What's wrong with a bodyguard?
A female bodyguard.
She must be vulgar.
It seems to be her.
Who are you talking about?
You took Cheng Qi away.
You don't need to be like this.
If you are sensible, you should divorce with him.
Don't delay his future.
I'm just a vulgar female escort.
Can I listen to you?
Besides,
if you just like Cheng Qi's lyrics and picture books,
who he marries
has nothing to do with you.
Without me, Cheng Qi is nothing.
Only we can make him on the Star List.
What's wrong with being an escort?
Is it not worthy to be with Cheng Qi?
I even wanted to help him take things home.
What?
Dare Cheng Qi make you feel wronged?
No.
It's those people outside the building.
They said I was vulgar and unbearable.
The girl who put up the notice, right?
Ms. Li said
she hid in Cheng Qi's wardrobe
and scared him.
In the wardrobe?
Is she okay?
You don't understand.
She regards Cheng Qi
as her future husband,
so she spent a lot of money
to buy his songbooks.
What about others?
They think so?
Probably.
So what?
Why did you scold me?
Put your legs down.
You are Cheng Qi's wife.
You said it has nothing to do with you.
Cheng Qi took an order from the Escort Agency.
Do you think
he really treats me as his wife?
Wait.
He took orders from the escort agency?
Didn't he gift ink at Moon God Pavilion?
Jiaojiao,
as your bestie,
let me give you some advice.
A woman should dress up for the one she loves.
What does that mean?
It means
as the wife of a talented man,
you should learn
to learn how to dress up.
You also think I'm not good enough for him.
I didn't mean that.
Cheng Qi is now
a hot candidate for the top scholar.
He can't avoid attending some elegant banquets.
Are you going to wear this escort suit?
If I have to go,
you can dress me up.
I can't be with you every day.
Every day, Cheng Qi
around him every day.
You'd better learn it yourself.
If he falls in love
with some lady one day,
it'll be too late.
You've managed some merchants,
and you don't know who you are.
How dare you disobey my order!
Calm down, brother.
Father said
the emperor loves poetry.
If Mr. Ling is excellent,
he'll be the champion.
Otherwise,
he'll anger the Emperor.
I'm afraid
even father can't protect himself.
So I dare not promise.
Don't threaten me with the Emperor.
I know all your tricks.
You just want to embarrass me
in front of others.
I don't have time for this.
You must
make this work,
no matter what.
Brother, calm down.
I'll talk to father.
He'll handle it.
Later, I'll have Mr. Li
wipe out Mr. Ling's recent debts.
That's a lot of money.
Are you also trying to make me look bad?
I dare not.
Miss Zhang,
what brings Mr. Cheng here?
Actually,
I received your support and help
at the Starry Night Gala.
I left in a hurry last time,
so I came to express my gratitude.
I'm not available today.
Please come another day.
If that's the case,
please give these scrolls of poetry and music
to my lady.
It's a token of my appreciation.
Farewell.
Let him in.
Bring a few more pots of wine.
Yes, my lady.
Please, sir.
My lady, you shouldn't drink anymore.
I'm happy to.
Mind your own business.
Even if you're upset,
you shouldn't risk your health.
When you were at the pleasure house,
did girls ever say this to you?
To be honest,
you know everything.
Yes.
I know everything.
I know every candidate in the final round.
But
talent and ambition alone
are useless.
What do you mean?
I want you to be the top of the Xingyun List.
I want you to stay by my side.
Cheng Qi is already married.
And you are the daughter of the Grand Preceptor.
I dare not be too bold.
The escort agency is not for you.
Neither is Su Yuejiao.
Please drink more hot tea.
Alcohol is bad for health.
It's getting late.
I
have to leave.
I'll drink with you another day.
You're so outstanding.
You deserve someone who loves you wholeheartedly.
My Lord,
I just wanna ask for my brothers.
Are we sure to continue to be bandits?
We haven't made any money for days.
We are bandits.
But you don't allow us to do anything.
We haven't had a decent meal for a long time.
Yeah.
Why don't you
take us to the Escort Agency?
You said we would go there.
You said
the food there is good.
and the beds
are comfortable?
Let's go to the city tomorrow.
My Lord,
you finally came to your senses.
Even if it's manual labor,
we can't let the brothers starve.
Father, you wanted to see me?
Let Qijia speak.
Dad,
she's really out of line now.
I asked her to arrange a winner of the contest,
but she kept putting it off.
She didn't take me seriously at all.
You want to arrange Ling Xingchen?
You think he's suitable, right?
He's a little weak,
but his family background
is good.
Did you hear that?
How dare she say that she's afraid of the emperor's anger?
Who's she bluffing?
Mr. Ling's poem
must be written by someone else.
I've managed to get him into the final round.
As for who will win in the end,
I dare not say.
That's not what you said before.
Enough.
It's always good to be cautious.
Yun,
you may go now.
Yes, father.
You just
can't keep a lid on it.
You don't like to write,
so she has to handle
those things to please the official.
But
I've already promised Ling Feng.
Besides,
we need his connections.
Enough.
I know what I'm doing.
Just focus on the Ministry of Works.
Later,
I'll recommend you to the Ministry of Civil Office.
By then,
those noble young men
will be seeking your help.
Okay.
I won't let you down.
Should I apply the powder first
or rouge first?
Whatever.
Something's not right.
Has it gone bad
from sitting too long?
My son-in-law, you're back.
You... you...
Didn't you go drinking with Grandpa?
Why are you back so early?
Grandpa went to the ancestral hall after a few drinks.
I might as well come back and drink alone.
Then drink more.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you crying?
It's nothing. Just got dust in my eyes.
You really cried.
I should help you.
Don't be so moved.
Come on.
My dear.
You...
Are you sick?
Come on, let me take you to the doctor.
Go.
I'm fine.
You didn't see anything.
No.
Why can't I wipe it off?
My dear.
Wait for me.
Alright.
Pigment from Pingjiang and powder from Guangling
are hard to wash off.
My lady,
why do you suddenly use rouge?
What's wrong?
Can't I use it?
Of course you can.
But you can't use it when escorting.
I just
saw it when I was tidying up the box,
and I wanna see if it's broken.
These are all new models in recent years.
They won't be broken if not used.
I'm just ignorant, okay?
It's none of your business.
Go to sleep.
[Does she]
[have feelings for me?]
[What am I doing?]
[So embarrassing.]
Hello.
Five copies of Cheng's book.
Sorry, we don't have.
I want
two boxes of Ling's book.
Two boxes.
Two hundred copies.
Three hundred taels.
Take them in the backyard.
What?
Others' books are sold in small quantities,
Why can't Cheng Qi get five?
He can.
But not for sale separately.
Five hundred copies at least.
Deal?
Five hundred?
Come on.
Who would buy so many at once?
You're forcing me.
Don't waste my time if you don't buy.
When he falls out of the top ten,
you don't have to buy it.
No way.
Cheng Qi will definitely enter the final.
Just wait.
You crafty merchant,
you'll get your karma.
You...
Shopkeeper,
I saw in the backyard,
there are many books of Cheng Qi.
Why don't you sell them?
You're just a temp worker.
If you want to get paid,
then get to work.
Don't ask so many questions.
Including the tickets from a few days ago,
there are about a thousand.
Yesterday, I saw the list.
The top one was only a thousand.
If we count the copies sold before,
this should be enough.
Feifei,
you were right.
They're all buying books today.
How many carts?
At least two carts per family.
That's
hundreds of copies.
The rankings have changed a lot.
Where's Cheng Qi?
The competition is fierce.
How did Cheng Qi fall off the list?
What's going on?